<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Silvia&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Silvia&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:52:29 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Running Python Files: Module vs Script</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tools/command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:52:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tools/command-line/</guid>
      <description>Running Python Files: Script vs Module Script Execution Purpose: Direct program execution Function: Runs file directly from command line Executes code sequentially __name__ == &amp;quot;__main__&amp;quot; Key Features: Command line usage One-off automation tasks Testing during development Module Execution Purpose: Code reusability Function: Imported into other Python files Code accessed as library __name__ == &amp;quot;module_name&amp;quot; Key Features: Reusable components Library functions Part of larger applications Relationship Best Practices:
def main(): # Main execution code pass if __name__ == &amp;#34;__main__&amp;#34;: main() # Only runs when executed as script Use Cases:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Format Checking Tools</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tools/format--checker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tools/format--checker/</guid>
      <description>Flake8 vs Autopep8 Flake8 Purpose: Code linting tool Function: Checks if code follows PEP 8 style guide Detects syntax errors Reports code style issues Key Features: Only identifies and reports issues Does not modify code Combines multiple tools: PyFlakes (Python code error checking) pycodestyle (style checking) McCabe (code complexity checking) Autopep8 Purpose: Code formatting tool Function: Automatically fixes code style issues Makes code PEP 8 compliant Key Features: Automatically modifies code Focuses on formatting issues Can fix most formatting issues reported by flake8 Relationship Complementary Tools:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SessionStorage vs LocalStorage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-development/front-end-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/web-development/front-end-storage/</guid>
      <description>SessionStorage vs LocalStorage LocalStorage Purpose: Persistent web storage Function: Stores data with no expiration date Persists across browser sessions Shared across browser tabs Key Features: Data survives browser restarts ~5-10MB storage capacity Same-origin access only Accessible via JavaScript SessionStorage Purpose: Temporary web storage Function: Stores data for one browser session Clears when tab is closed Isolated per browser tab Key Features: Tab-specific storage ~5-10MB storage capacity Temporary data persistence Same-origin access only Relationship Common Traits:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcodes Samples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>This is a sample post intended to test the followings:
Default hero image. Different shortcodes. Alert The following alerts are available in this theme.
This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;success&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;danger&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;warning&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;info&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;dark&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;primary&amp;quot;. This is sample alert with type=&amp;quot;secondary&amp;quot;. Image A sample image without any attribute.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
